My Date with Drew is a documentary film directed by Brett Winn.
Ever since the second grade when he first saw her in E.T.
The Extraterrestrial, Brian Herzlinger has had a crush on Drew Barrymore.
Now, 20 years later he's decided to try to fulfill his
lifelong dream by asking her for a date.
There's one small problem: She's Drew Barrymore and he's, well, Brian
Herzlinger, a broke 27-year-old aspiring filmmaker from New Jersey.
Self, played by Drew Barrymore.
Self, played by Brian Herzlinger.
Self, played by Corey Feldman.
Self, played by Eric Roberts.
Self, played by Bill D'Elia.
Drew Look-alike, played by Lily Rains.
My Date with Drew is a 2004 independent documentary film
starring and directed by Brian Herzlinger.
The film uses guerrilla filmmaking and received several awards.
The film explores themes of obsession, dream girl, crush.